

### CONTACTS

Republic of Belarus, Brest tel. +375 (29) 723 00 90 email: victor.chizh@mail.ru telegram: t.me/ViktorChizh

github.com/ViktorChizh linkedin.com/in/ViktorChizh codewars.com/users/ViktorChizh offerheap.com/specialist/ViktorChizh

### **EDUCATION**

IT-INCUBATOR Vocational training Typescript, React, Redux, Redux-Toolkit, RTKquery, Redux-Saga, Jest, Storybook, Postman, Styled Components, RadixUI, etc.

Educational center "Leader" HTML, CSS, JavaScript 2022

**Belarusian National Technical University** Engineer GPA: cum laude

## ONLINE COURSES

Front End Development Libraries <u>freeCodeCamp</u>

Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures <u>freeCodeCamp</u>

### LANGUAGES

Russian - native

English - Pre-Intermediate A2 (in progress)

# VIKTOR CHIZH

## ABOUT ME

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Hi, I am a Front-end developer with almost 2 years of experience (including commercial). I work with technologies such as React, Vue.js, TypeScript, Redux, Redux Toolkit, RTK-query and other related libraries. I am constantly improving my skills.

I'm always open to new opportunities, will be glad to communicate and will consider your suggestions. Additional information in Portfolio or on LinkedIn.

### WORK EXPERIENCES

### "WebDad"

Aug. 2024 - present time

Front-end developer.

Key responsibilities: Adaptive layout based on Figma layouts. Project support, creation of new and optimization of existing components, bug

Stack: Vue, React, NextJs, TypeScript, Zustand, TailWindCSS, SCSS, Git.

## "Roug Arts"

May 2024 - Jul. 2024

Project for creating a gaming application in Telegram as a front-end developer.

### Key responsibilities:

- Responsive layout based on Figma designs.
- Code optimization and identifying necessary components.
- Interaction with the backend.

Stack: React, TypeScript, HTML, SCSS, Git.

## IT-incubator

Nov. 2023 - May 2024

I consolidated my knowledge and filled in the gaps. The learning process was as close to real work as possible. At the end of the training, I completed an internship on the inctagram project in a team consisting of: PM + 2 QA + 6 Front-end + 2 back-end.

Projects: Social network, Flash cards, Inctagram

Key responsibilities: Team development using Git. Full authentication flow. Processing and checking forms. Creating routes and redirection. Covering applications with tests using Jest. Improving performance and optimization.

Stack: React, TypeScript, Redux Toolkit, RTK-query, React Hook Form, Storybook, Jest, Git.

## "Relotech Solution"

Jun. 2023 - Dec. 2023

Commercial internship as a front-end developer on a Relocate project (aggregator of statistical data about countries of the world).

The work was carried out:

- a full-stack team of 15 people (back-end, front-end, UI/UX, QA, DevOps engineer, BA, PM)
- according to the Agile methodology with daily sprints
- using a task-tracker ClickUp

Stack: Next.js, MobX, React, React-router, React DOM, HTML, SCSS, Git

### ✓ HTML ✓ CSS, SCSS, SASS ✓ JavaScript SKILLS ✓ TypeScript ✓ React ✓ Next.js ✓ MobX

- 🗸 Redux, Redux Toolkit, RTK-query, Redux-Saga 🗸 Jest 🗸 Git
- 🗸 Styled Components 🗸 Bootstrap 🗸 MaterialUI 🗸 RadixUl
- 🗸 Storybook 🗸 Postman 🗸 ect.